endeavour.edu.au 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy - Endeavour College of Natural Health

## Stay Informed »

Subscribe to Endeavour's eNewsletter and stay up to date on news and events about the college.

Endeavour College recognises the privacy concerns of visitors to its sites on the Internet. Specifically, Endeavour College recognises the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about visitors to Endeavour College’s website. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information is automatically collected from visitors to Endeavour College sites, unless you provide Endeavour College that information voluntarily.

## Information Collection & Use

Endeavour College gathers information about website visitors to improve the quality of online information and services offered. There are two forms of data that Endeavour College collects: site visitor data and personal information voluntarily provided to Endeavour College by site visitors.

## Site Visitor Data

Endeavour College routinely gathers data on website activity, such as how many people visit the site, the pages they visit, etc. Site visitor data is:  collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis, which means no personal information is associated with this data and gathered through the use of Web server logs and cookies. A Web server log is a file where Web site activity is stored. A cookie is a small piece of information that a Web site sends to a visitor’s computer, which is stored on the visitor’s hard drive. Endeavour College uses cookies to track repeat visits, track usage patterns and better serve you. The cookie does not extract personal information about you. Most browsers provide a simple procedure to reject cookies or enable you to control whether you want to receive cookies through prior notification. 

## Personal Information

Endeavour College collects personal information submitted from site visitors, such as a visitor’s name, address, phone number, e-mail address, etc. Personal information is collected only when site visitors voluntarily provide it.

## Email Communications

Any comments or questions sent via email to Endeavour College might be shared with our Student or Enrolment Advisers, who are most capable of addressing your questions and concerns. Endeavour College will retain your communication until we have done our best to provide you with a complete response and then will either discard it, or, in some cases, archive it.  Please be advised that most email systems do not provide a means for completely secure and private communications. Non-encrypted email communications may be accessed and viewed by others while in transit to or from Endeavour College. For that reason, do not use email to communicate information to Endeavour College that you consider to be confidential. 

Endeavour College will not sell, trade or otherwise disclose personal information or email communication outside the Endeavour College family of companies unless required to do so by legal, judicial or governmental proceedings, or unless required to do so in accordance with any authorisation you have given us.

### Revisions

Endeavour College may at any time revise this Internet Privacy Policy by updating this posting.

However, important aspects of our policy are:

Personal details provided by you to Endeavour College through electronic responses from this site will not be forwarded, sold, or made available in any way to any third party.  However, Endeavour College may communicate with you again with other information that is complimentary to your original request.  Each of these communications will have clear ‘opt-out’ instructions so you can choose not to receive further Endeavour College communication.  On the other hand, you may wish to receive other Endeavour College communication, you would always be asked before such information is forwarded.  

**How Endeavour College uses the information you provide…**  
Endeavour College may use information it collects from you for the primary purpose for which it is collected and for such other secondary purposes that are related to the primary purpose of collection.

**Endeavour College generally uses personal information to:**

  * provide you with products or services you have requested; 
  * personalise and customise your experiences on the Endeavour College website; 
  * help Endeavour College manage and enhance its services to you; 
  * communicate with you; 
  * provide you with ongoing information about opportunities on the Endeavour College website in which Endeavour College believes you may be interested; and 
  * give you the opportunity from time to time to receive emails and ‘e-newsletters’ from Endeavour College.
